Guide to the Ithaca Area United Jewish Community records, 1900s.
Ithaca Area United Jewish Community records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Ithaca Area United Jewish Community records, 1900s.
6876
3 cubic feet.
Correspondence, Photographs, Printed Material, Publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
The collection includes correspondence, meeting minutes, annual reports, newsletters and other printed matter, publications, photographs, and architectural plans reflecting the activities of the organization..
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The collection includes correspondence, meeting minutes, annual reports, newsletters and other printed matter, publications, photographs, and architectural plans reflecting the activities of the organization. Includes official Board business; Treasurers' Reports, Board meeting minutes, fund raising campaigns, public relations and advertising, financial allocations, the United Jewish Appeal, the Ithaca Jewish Welfare Fund and the Committee for the Resettlement of Jewish Refuges in Ithaca.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Ithaca Area United Jewish Community.
Subjects:
Jewish communities--New York (State)--Ithaca.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Permission of the Chair or other officers of the Board required for access to the collection.
CONTAINER LIST
- Campaigns, 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Campaigns, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Campaigns, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Campaign, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Campaign, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Campaign, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Campaign, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Campaign, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Campaign, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Campaign, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Campaign, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- 25th Anniversary Campaign, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Campaign, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Campaign, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Campaigns, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Campaign, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Campaign, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Campaign, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Campaign, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Campaign, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Campaign, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Campaign, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Campaign, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Campaign, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Campaign, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Campaign, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Campaign, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Campaign, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Campaign, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Campaign, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Campaign, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Campaign, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Campaign, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Campaign, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Allocations, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Allocations, 1965-1978 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Allocations, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Allocations, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Allocations, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Allocations, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Allocations, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Allocations, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Allocations, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Allocations, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Allocations, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Allocations, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Allocations, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Allocations, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Allocations, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Allocations, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Bank Statements, 1987-1999 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- UJA Statements, 1978-1979, 1987-1997 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Deposits, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Legal Procedures, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Minutes, 1946-1948 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Minutes, 1949-1952 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Minutes, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Minutes, 1959-1961 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Minutes, 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Minutes, 1978-1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Minutes, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Minutes, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Treasurer's Report, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Treasurer's Report, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Mailing Lists, 1988-1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Membership Lists, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Stocks and Bonds, 1987-1999 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Nominating Committee, 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Resettlement Committee, 1987-1991 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Resettlement Committee, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Resettlement Committee, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Ithaca Housing, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Refugee: Shclover, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Refugee: Kudrayartsev, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Refugee: Myhikov and Stamislavskaya, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Refugee: Khibnik, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Refugee: Yevgeniya Avanesova, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Refugee: Stremlin, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Refugee: Astrov, 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Refugee: Spitsberg, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Rabbi Felix Aber Religious School of Temple Beth-El (Box 2, Folder 30)
- B'Nai B'Rith Jerusalem 3000 Program Guide, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- First United Jewish Appeal Young Leadership Conference, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- The United Synagogue of America Biennial Convention, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- 25th Anniversary Manual, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Phonathon, 1993-1999 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Anti-Defamation League (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Brenda Kaufman-Berman Memorial Book, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Ithaca Reform Temple, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Philip Rogachecfsky Correspondence, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1979, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1997-2000 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- UJA Newspaper Clippings (Box 2, Folder 48)
- UJA Newspaper Clippings, 1993-2000 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Miscellaneous Fliers and Pamphlets (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
- Publications, 1960-1965 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Articles, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Articles and Publications (Box 3, Folder 5)
- UJA Public Relations and Advertising Program, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Guide to Jewish Ithaca (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Guide to Jewish Ithaca, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Guide to Jewish Ithaca, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Jewish Organizations in Ithaca (Box 3, Folder 10)